{
    "id": "366e3a6d31e34d54b781916557bf078e",
    "title": "Active And Passive Voice Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "The letters ................................ in the morning.",
            "description": "A passive verb is required here because the subject is not the doer of the action. ",
            "answers": [
                "posted",
                "have posted",
                "were posted"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "438b91ae30504aae9cb3eab50a46f031"
        },
        {
            "question": "She .................................... of our decision.",
            "description": "A passive verb is required here because the subject is not the doer of the action. ",
            "answers": [
                "has informed",
                "informed",
                "has been informed"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "a6ef71a1d1bc4e90ae67ef1d5c9f2af7"
        },
        {
            "question": "The old man .................................... alone for many years.",
            "description": "Either the present perfect or the present perfect continuous tense is possible here.",
            "answers": [
                "has been living",
                "has been lived",
                "has lived"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "b6b57b7e711e47afab2a506f163d8cb2"
        },
        {
            "question": "His kind words ................................ me.",
            "description": "An active verb is required here because the subject is the doer of action. ",
            "answers": [
                "were encouraged",
                "encouraged",
                "were being encouraging"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "479185e3af734d8ba6db6d5e2f398bf8"
        },
        {
            "question": "I .................................... by his kind words.",
            "description": "A passive verb is required here because the subject is not the doer of the action. ",
            "answers": [
                "encouraged",
                "was encouraged",
                "was encouraging"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "053d1f4b6518485c8c4d1b26a99933ed"
        },
        {
            "question": "He .................................... everything in detail.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "explained",
                "was explained",
                "has been explained"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "319a09b75d8441889f5b253fafb8303e"
        },
        {
            "question": "Everything ................................. in detail.",
            "description": "A passive verb is required here because the subject is not the doer of the action. ",
            "answers": [
                "explained",
                "was explained",
                "has explained"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "766a1e6e6e4d441cafb3e3f398eaa44f"
        },
        {
            "question": "She ................................. him instantly.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "recognized",
                "has been recognized",
                "was recognized"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "fb151b3dd9b0468aa2cf6b7c86e08a73"
        },
        {
            "question": "He ...................................",
            "description": "A passive verb is required here because the subject is not the doer of the action. ",
            "answers": [
                "instantly deported",
                "has instantly deported",
                "was instantly deported"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "d90246e1b0bc436e8e817f20148d27bc"
        },
        {
            "question": "I .................................. unawares.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "caught",
                "was caught",
                "have caught"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "b4da21b7bb9844c985b788663d957c47"
        },
        {
            "question": "She ................................ into the room happily.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "danced",
                "was danced",
                "has danced"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "b7c0bd3742594016a074b329fdaf9e99"
        },
        {
            "question": "She ................................ aback.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "took",
                "was taken",
                "has taken"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "668826c3603b47f2bde94e1bcc922c5a"
        }
    ]
}